OPERATIONS MANAGER

Summary

High-performing Operations Manager bringing 13 years of experience in office administration and delivering successful improvements for business operations and team development. Recognized as driven, dedicated and hard working, with history of optimizing workflows and increasing team productivity. Decisive leader and strategic problem solver with excellent communication and planning abilities.

Skills

- Staff training and development
- Process improvement strategies
- Business and Operations Management
- Team Building/Leadership
- MS Office
- Computer skills

Experience

Operations Manager, Doordash, August 2018 - September 2021 Bainbridge, GA

- Conducted performance reviews providing coaching and feedback to benefit both company and employee.
- Delivered positive customer experiences by implementing effective quality assurance practices.
- Collaborated with staff to maximize customer satisfaction, streamline procedures and improve bottom-line profitability.
- Planned and directed daily operational strategies, including team workflows and performance/process improvement initiatives.
- Recruited, hired and trained crew members on application of projects, customer relations and customer service.
- Reviewed monthly financial reports and reconciled accounts to keep information current and accurate.
- Aided senior leadership during executive decision-making process by generating daily reports to recommend corrective actions and improvements.

Practice Supervisor, Intermountain Healthcare, September 2016 - August 2018 Hurricane, UT

- Created and implemented policies and procedures for effective practice management.
- Managed clinical operations and procedures and enforced adherence to federal and state regulations and healthcare law requirements.
- Led and motivated 25 employees through supervision, training and coaching on duties and daily operational activities which boosted
 efficiency and improved overall process flow.
- Resolved conflicts promptly among physicians, nurses and other healthcare employees to keep workflows on task.
- Implemented new hire training to further develop skills and initiate discussions on task prioritization.

Executive Assistant, Amtrust Financial Services, Inc., October 2013 - September 2016 Concord, CA

- Revised and maintained master calendar for provider appointments.
- Detailed and arranged travel arrangements and venue reservations for conferences and seminars.
- Set up meeting and event logistics for team of 14 providers and maintained calendars.
- Processed provider hospital credentialing, license renewals, continuing education requirements and membership renewals.
- Created and maintained computer- and paper-based filing and organization systems for patient tracking, procedure scheduling, medical reports and documents.
- Ordered catering or restaurant delivery to offer food and beverages to meeting and conference attendees.
- Liaised between Practice Medical Director and patients regarding patient procedures.

Medical Billing Specialist, Breg, Inc., May 2008 - October 2013 Columbia, SC

- Prepared billing statements for patients, ensuring correct diagnostic coding.
- Entered procedure codes, diagnosis codes and patient information into NextGen.
- Contacted insurance providers to verify insurance information, review benefits and obtain billing authorization.
- Maintained current working knowledge of CPT and ICD-10 coding principles, protocols and third-party billing requirements.
- Determined prior authorizations for medication and outpatient procedures.
- Evaluated accuracy of provider charges, including dates of service, procedures, level of care and diagnoses.
- Posted charges, payments and write-ups for cardiovascular procedures.

Education and Training

Associate of Applied Science Medical Assisting, , ECPI University, , City June 2008